<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Telenor BizStore</string>
    <string name="slide_2_text_1">MOVIES, CINEMAS, EVENTS</string>
    <string name="slide_2_text_2">&amp; ENTERTAINMENT</string>
    <string name="slide_2_text_3">ON YOUR FINGER TIPS</string>
    <string name="slide_3_text_1">TRAVEL &amp; TOURS, HOTELS &amp;</string>
    <string name="slide_3_text_2">SPAS, SPORTS &amp; FITNESS</string>
    <string name="slide_3_text_3">&amp; MUCH MORE</string>
    <string name="help_question1">What is Telenor Biz Store Service all about?</string>
    <string name="help_answer1"><![CDATA[Telenor Biz Store is an SMS and Mobile Application based service which provides a platform to view best Deals & Discounts on Top Brands in Pakistan. With major brands on-board ranging from fashion & lifestyle to health & fitness, Shopping, Restaurants and much more, Biz Store has it All!\n\nTelenor Biz Store also offers a variety of Exclusive Deals available to BizStore users only who can later avail them from the respective stores/outlets via discount redemption process.]]></string>
    <string name="help_question2">What do I get from Telenor Biz Store?</string>
    <string name="help_answer2"><![CDATA[Telenor Biz Store users get Exclusive Deals & Discounts along with latest updates of the related categories. The user can also search any business of their liking and get the contact details. The categories for which deals & updates are offered are as follows:
    \n\t\t1. Top Deals
    \n\t\t2. Food Deals
    \n\t\t3. Shopping and Fashion
    \n\t\t4. Ladies Section
    \n\t\t5. Health and Fitness
    \n\t\t6. Education
    \n\t\t7. Entertainment]]></string>
    <string name="help_question3">How can a user subscribe to Telenor Biz Store?</string>
    <string name="help_answer3">User can subscribe to Telenor Biz Store via either of the two mediums:</string>
    <string name="help_answer3a">1. <b>SMS:</b> User must send “SUB” to 5005. Once sent, the user will get a message confirming successful subscription. User will be charged Rs. 5+tax/Week as subscription price. However, if the user has already subscribed to the service through Smartphone Application, he will not be charged again.</string>
    <string name="help_answer3b">2. <b>Smart Phone Application:</b>
\n\t\ti. User downloads the Bizstore smartphone application from Telenor App Store.
\n\t\tii. User enters his Telenor Mobile Number to login.
\n\t\tiii. On successful login, he becomes the subscriber and is charged Rs. 5 + tax /Week for the service.
\n\tiv. However, in case the user has already subscribed to the service through SMS, he will not be charged again.</string>
    <string name="help_question4">What are the Smartphone Application Charges?</string>
    <string name="help_answer4">Upon successful application installation &amp; login, the user will be charged are Rs. 5+tax/Week. However, the user is not charged on downloading the smartphone application.</string>
    <string name="help_question5">How can a User Redeem Exclusive Deals?</string>
    <string name="help_answer5">The User can redeem the deal through following steps:</string>
    <string name="help_answer5a">Step 1: User views the deal on APP.
    \nStep 2: User will have to click on Redeem Deal Button. (Only for Exclusive Deals)
    \nStep 3: User will have to enter merchant code.</string>
    <string name="help_answer5b">i.	Merchant can enter the code for User on their mobile.
    \nii. Merchant can share the code with User.
    \niii. Merchant codes will be put on display in their shops and User can enter it himself.</string>
    <string name="help_question6">How can a user Unsubscribe from this service?</string>
    <string name="help_answer6a">User can deactivate the service by simply clicking on ‘Unsubscribe’ button from Main Menu given on the home screen. Once done, the user will have to login again if he wishes to use the smartphone application.</string>
    <string name="num_confirm_text">Please enter your Telenor Number.</string>
    <string name="qatar_code">92</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_num">Please enter a valid Telenor Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="subscription_charges">You will be charged Rs <b>5</b>/week</string>
    <string name="share_with_friends_txt">Hi, I just found this great App for you called Telenor Biz Store. You can find businesses and enjoy the best deals &amp; discounts in your city. Send SUB to 5005 to download the Application.</string>

</resources>
